Subindex build by Linnet
嘿，你们觉得我这条鸭子领带怎么样？
Hey, what do you guys think of my new ducky tie?
很可爱～
Pretty cute, right?
而且不是很贵，仅仅是普通的价格
And not that much more expensive than a regular tie.
嗯哼
Hmm.
一个鸭子领带？
A ducky tie?
哥们，你为什么要这么干
Bro, why do you do this
你知道我一定会吐槽你
when you know I must slam you for it?
千万不要把视线移开
You guys might want to look away
我知道你们都很期待
'cause this ain't gonna be pretty.
准备好了么？
You ready?
鸭子，鸭子，，，恶心死
Duck, duck... gross.
#燃烧吧#,
Hashtag burn,
#鸭子领带来吐槽#,
hashtag duck tie slam,
#Stinson帅呆了#.
hashtag Stinson rocks.
还有啥事不？
What else is going on?
噢，猜猜我遇到谁了？
Oh, guess who I ran into.
我过去的一个女朋友～
A girl from my past.
猜猜是谁？
Any guesses?
- Stella. - Zoe.
- Karen? - 那个打了你一顿的女人？
- Karen? - The girl who beat you up.
那个给你照片上画叉叉的女人？
The girl who ruined a photo with Slash!
那个给你消去蝴蝶纹身的女人?
The girl who made you get the butterfly tattoo?
你们搞得我像跟一群
You make it sound like I've dated
Stieg Larrson 系列小说的主人公约会过的人一样.
a series of Stieg Larrson novels.
也许你们需要更多的提示
Perhaps I need to be a little more specific.
我在婚礼中遇到了这个姑娘
I met this girl at a wedding.
我们在一起了一段时间， 但后来她去了德国
We were together for a while, but then she moved to Germany.
我们尝试过异地恋 但是没成功
We decided to try long distance, but it didn't work
因为我背着她跟另外一个人好上了 而这个人就在这张桌边
because I cheated on her with someone at this very table.
Victoria.
Victoria!
她为建筑师年会 制作甜品
She catered dessert for the Architects' Ball.
喔噢，你好像有大概，呃 六年没见了?
Wow. I mean, what's it been, like, what, six years?
对啊，这真有意思啊， 想起当初...
Yeah, it's so funny how the past...
你懂的，
you know, you think
你觉得你做对了 但是，你懂的,
you're doing fine, but you know,
因为真爱... 我去, Lily!
because true love... God, Lily!
你胸前的这对小白兔 肿么了?
What on Earth is going on with your cans?
噢，这对小可爱?
Oh, these old things?
我有了一对 萌化的小白兔!
I got my pregnancy boobs!
我现在感觉处在最佳状态
I'm in that sweet spot
我的胸部已经 感觉到我怀孕了,
where the chestal area knows I'm pregnant,
但是我的 腹部还没变化.
but hasn't told the downstairs neighbors.
那么，你还在等什么  Lil?
Well, what are you waiting for, Lil?
让你的小兔兔出来秀一下! 让它们跳一个!
Bust 'em out! Make 'em dance!
才不!
No!
?你的兔兔秀 ?
? Let your boobies show! ?
好啦，不好意思哥们
Okay, I'm sorry, pal,
我老婆毛衣里的部分是私人财产
but the party in my wife's sweater is a private event,
而我是这财产的保护神.
and I'm the bouncer.
哥们，我觉得这对 财产你要好好保护.
Dude, I think they's the bouncers.
好了，我们能不再聊 我老婆的胸部了么
Okay, can we stop talking about my wife's breasts, please?
Ted继续说 Victoria!
Ted ran into Victoria!
我知道，我仍然有点 不好意思见她
I know, I'm still a little shaken by it.
经历了这么多年 她突然出现在我面前.
I mean, there she was after all these years.
所有的感情，记忆...
The emotions and memories and...
偶的神啊，lily 你的屁屁像长在胸上了.
Geez, Lily, it's like you have a butt on your chest.
Whoo-whoo-whoo!
?How I Met Your Mother 7x03 ?/font> Ducky Tie Original Air Date on September 26, 2011
? How I Met Your Mother 7x03 ? Ducky Tie Original Air Date on September 26, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman == 翻译by Saraphines ==
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
?
你究竟为啥要看?
Why on Earth would I want to see that?
因为这想法就环绕在哥的周围
They're round and attached to my body.
公平交易.
It's an even trade.
谁想一起吃饭?
Okay, who wants dinner?
保重身体哟 我们去Shinjitsu吧.
Bless you. Let's go to Shinjitsu.
我去，又去?
Aw, again? Really?
你一个月 平均去一次
You bring that up, like, once a month.
那边有木炭火盆烧烤 还有席间厨师表演
It's hibachi grilling with a vaudeville twist.
说真的，谁一起去?
I mean, come on, who's in?
(Ted, Lily & Robin 均表示同意)
No! Forget it!
不！坚决不去！
那么这样吧：
Okay, how about this:
假如你可以10秒钟 不看Lily的胸部
if you can go ten seconds without looking at Lily's boobs,
你说去哪里 我们就去哪里
we'll go wherever you want to go.
一言为定
Deal.
坑爹呢
Damn it!
噢，也好
Oh, well.
你遇见Victoria
So you saw Victoria.
肯定非常兴奋咯
You must have been freaked.
不，一切都还好
No, it was cool.
Hey, Ted.
Hey, 你好.
Hey, kiddo.
Ted,从我的角度来看...
Okay, Ted, 'cause from where I was standing...
Robin! 还好吧?
Robin! Just... okay?
还是我自己来讲吧.
I'm telling this story.
让我们把那段 尴尬的小开场
Instead of the obligatory awkward small talk,
给略过去吧
let me just kick this off
比如我要说 我非常非常抱歉
by saying I'm really, really sorry.
谢谢，虽然没关系 但是还是谢谢
Thanks. It's unnecessary, but thanks.
所以没有尴尬
So, wasn't awkward.
- 还是有点小尴尬. - 没那么尴尬.
- It was a little awkward. - Not really.
是有点尴尬.
It was a little awkward.
你很幸运 因为你有场外援助 帮你度过难关
Lucky for you, the cavalry rode in to smooth things over.
嗯...
So, uh...
我抢走了你的男朋友
I stole your boyfriend!
听起来很疯狂啊!
That was, like, crazy!
我了个去?!
Like, what?!
但是... 睹物思人，物是人非.
But... bridge, water under it.
都是Ted的错. 他把我灌醉了.
It was all Ted's fault. He got me drunk.
什么? 噢，我在那边等你.
What? Yeah! Be right there.
噢，猜猜谁也来了? Robin.
Oh, guess who's here? Robin.
我非常非常 为你们高兴
Oh. I'm really happy for you guys.
你们在一起很般配.
You look cute together.
不不不，我们没在一起.
Oh, no, no, we're not together.
我的意思是说我们的确约会过一段时间.
I mean, we-we dated for, like, a year.
但现在我们仅仅是朋友
But now we're just friends.
噢，这个一点都不奇怪
It's not weird.
不，这为什么会奇怪?
No, no. Why would that be weird?
假如你们天天 出去玩的话那么就有点...
I mean, if you hung out every day, that would...
我们天天一起玩
We do.
...仍然不奇怪
...still not be weird.
我不知道还有谁
I've never known anybody
天天和自己的ex出去玩
that hangs out with their ex every day.
Barney也是
Well, Barney does.
真的么? Barney的ex是谁啊？
Really? Who's Barney's ex-girlfriend?
Robin.
你的Robin?
Your Robin?
我的和Barney的.
Mine and Barney's.
你们三个是一起 出去玩的么?
You don't all three hang out together?
总是在一起
All the time.
那是有点奇怪
And we have weird.
一点都不奇怪
It's not weird!
有谁尝过一口么
Has anyone gotten a bite yet?
好戏上演了！
Oh, good! Here we go!
今晚的大戏
The main event.
今晚的演员是Takumi. 他很厉害的!
Oh, we got Takumi. He is good!
好吧，我开个玩笑
I mean, who am I kidding?
其实他们都很厉害!
They're all amazing!
让我们的席间好戏开演
Let the dinnertainment begin!
噢，这个提醒了我
Oh, that reminds me,
我们有时间应该试试 别的酒店
there's this other restaurant we should try sometime.
那些酒店是在 一个小房间里烧菜的
What they do is, they cook your meal in a little room
那小房间叫做"厨房"
called a "kitchen."
那酒店的名字叫什么来着的?
What's the name of that...?
噢，对了 "纽约的所有其它酒店"
Oh, yeah! "Every Other Restaurant In New York City."
#燃烧吧#, #你的领带还是逊毙了#,
Hashtag burn, hashtag Your Tie Is Still Dumb,
#续杯#,
hashtag refill!
然后你跟Victoria聊天了
So you're talking to Victoria.
我是跟Victorial聊天了
I'm talking to Victoria.
那么，我似乎应该 回面包房去了
Well, I should probably get back to the bakery.
我今晚还要去赶去Hamptons 的晚班巴士
I'm taking a late bus out to the Hamptons tonight,
而我还要洗满满 一水槽的盘子
and I've got a sink full of dishes
我助手竟然不洗
that my assistant did not clean.
因为里里外外其实就只有我一个人
Because my assistant is me.
遇到你很高兴，Ted
But it was really good seeing you, Ted.
- 谢谢，我也是. - 好的
- Yeah, you, too. - Okay.
等等
Wait.
让我来洗碗吧 （吐槽：男人最性感的时候！！！有木有！！！）
Let me do the dishes.
什么？
What?
Victoria, 你是否相信命运
Victoria, do you believe in fate?
我相信你 要给我来一次关于命运的长篇大论
I believe you're about to give a big speech on fate.
呃，是的
Well, I do.
我相信你我二人在这茫茫人海中
And I think when two people like you and me randomly bump
不期而遇 这必然意味着一些事情.
into each other, it means something.
我需要为我过去的 所作所为道歉
I have to make amends for what I did.
我不能改变我六年前 的所作所为
Look, I can't undo what I did six years ago, but...
但，我可以帮你洗碗
I can wash dishes.
事实上，我很擅长洗碗
It's actually something I'm good at.
Ted...
我发誓 我不是要去挽回什么
I swear to you I am not trying anything.
?I said, bang, bang, bangity-bang ?
? I said, bang, bang, bangity-bang ?
?I said a bang, bang, bangity-bang. ?
? I said a bang, bang, bangity-bang. ?
兄弟姐妹们！闭嘴！
Guys, guys! Shut up!
给这位伟大的艺术家一点尊重！
Give the artist a little respect!
先生，我为我的所为道歉
Sir, I apologize for that,
以及为我马上要说的话道歉
and for what I'm about to say.
我对他的印象是这样的
Here's my impression of this guy.
噢，噢，噢
Uh! Ooh!
呃！呃！
Uh! Uh!
欢迎来 Shinjitsu! Uh!
Welcome to Shinjitsu! Uh!
我过去是DQ的晚班经理!噢！
I used to be a night manager at Dairy Queen! Brr!
是人都能做
Anyone can do that.
噢，真的么？你能做到么？Barney？
Oh really? Then why don't you do it, Barney?
把这些把戏给我表演一下把！ 像你说的那么简单的话！
Show us all the tricks if they're so easy.
给我们表演洋葱火山
Show us the onion volcano,
心跳炒饭
the fried rice beating heart,
让虾飞入上衣口袋
the shrimp in the pocket.
我打赌Ted肯定给Victoria 秀了一下他的小虾虾
I bet Ted showed Victoria the shrimp in his pocket.
小虾虾? 那么小?
Shrimp? Really?
好，
Okay, I'll do all
我会做到这些事 你说地点时间吧
those things. You just name the time and the place.
好的，就在这里， 在我们吃完以后
Okay, right here after we eat.
要是我做到了怎么办
And what do I get if I do?
你想要什么
What do you want?
我要摸Lily的胸
I want to touch Lily's boobs.
一言为定
Deal!
Hey, 亲爱的?
Hey, sweetie?
是的，我听到了
Yeah, I heard.
好的Barney, 既然你想要
Okay, Barney, you want to make this real?
那我就给你
Let's make this real.
条件: 如果你能做到
If you can do all that stuff
Marshall刚才提到的事情
that Marshall just listed off,
我会让你碰我的一只小兔
I will let you touch one boob.
一对小兔
Both boobs.
就一只
Just one.
又摸又捏
Touch and squeeze.
就只有摸
Just touch.
又摸又挤.
Touch and motorboat.
就只有摸
Just touch.
- 还能讨价还价? - Barney.
- Honka honka? - Barney.
就只有摸 就只有摸
Just touch. Just touch.
摸一小时. 摸一秒.
For one hour. For one second.
20 分钟, 两只兔兔
20 minutes, both boobs.
30秒， 就一只兔兔
Thirty seconds, one boob.
4分钟，两只兔兔 捏三下
Four minutes, both boobs, three squeezes.
一分钟，两只兔兔  不准捏
One minute, both boobs,  one squeeze.
一言为定
Deal!
但是...要是你做不到任何一件事
But... if you can't do everything
注意是任何一件事
and I mean everything,
拿你就要带 Marshall的鸭子领带...
then you have to wear Marshall's ducky tie...
一年
for one year.
噢...
Ooh...
一言为定
Deal.
那么你们去了面包房
So you get to the bakery.
我们去了面包房
We get to the bakery.
嗯，一切顺利
Well, this is great.
你知道还有哪些能够
You know what else is getting clean
把这些茶盘弄干净？
along with this cupcake tray?
我的良心
My conscience.
你还要 你去偿还什么么？
You got anything else you need to atone for?
呵呵，我的烤炉还要清理一下
My oven needs cleaning.
没别的了
Un, no, nothing else.
暂时没别的了
Not yet anyway.
?Bang, bang, bangity-bang, said a bang-bang-bangity. ?
? Bang, bang, bangity-bang, said a bang-bang-bangity. ?
我要结婚了.
I'm getting married.
Bang.
Baby,我觉得我拿了你的 这个里面没有酒
Baby, I think I got yours. This one has no booze.
Oh,不，这个是我的
Oh, no, that's mine.
Yeah, 我不知道
Yeah, I don't know
为什么我的Mai Tais 需要放酒
why people think that Mai Tais need booze.
我曾经狂饮了 整整一晚
I've been drinking virgins all night,
爽爆了
and they're delicious.
Yeah,你还是好好喝Mai Tai吧
Yeah, well, enjoy your Mai Tai
因为明天晚上 你要带我的领带了
because as of tomorrow night, you'll be wearing my tie.
我们未来的孩子 太幸运了
Our future child is so lucky.
等等，你没和醉了吧?
Wait. You're not drunk?
Huh. 我觉得没有.
Huh. I guess not.
这是个骗局！
It's a hustle!
我们被骗了!
We gettin' hustled!
噢，我已经闻到阴谋的味道了
Oh, this stinks.
这阴谋的味道臭不可闻
This stinks to holy hell!
他要赢这赌局了！
He's gonna win the bet!
Baby, 放心，即使他静若处子
Baby, come on. Even if he was sober as a nun,
也绝对做不到这里厨师的水平
there's no way he could do what these guys do.
确实如此，我的意思是要学到
Exactly. I mean, to learn the trademark secrets
Shinjitsu木炭火烧的精髓秘籍
of Shinjitsu hibachi cooking,
就要远赴..
one would have to go all the way...
Hoboken, New Jersey.
to Hoboken, New Jersey.
是的，他们在那边有所学校
Yeah, they have a school there.
六个月的课程， 他们会教你一切.
It's a six-month course. They teach you everything.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
也许我刚刚用手机 上网查了一下
Maybe I looked it up on my phone just now.
也许不是噢
Then again, maybe not.
那么说Victoria马上要结婚了
So Victoria's getting married.
她马上要结婚了
She's getting married.
对不起 我早就该告诉你的
I'm sorry. I should have told you that way earlier.
不，这很好
No, no, it's fine.
我觉得这事 迟早会发生
You thought something was gonna happen.
大概有百分之一的机率
Like one percent.
下次记得戴上戒指
Maybe slap on a ring next time.
但问题是 他还没向我求婚
Well, the problem is, he hasn't asked me yet.
我在一个袜子柜的盒子里 找到了一个戒指.
I found the ring in a box in his sock drawer.
哇噢，这哥们为袜子准备了一个柜子
Wow! Guy's got a whole drawer just for socks?
真是个好男人
Must be nice.
那么那个好男人 什么时候打算向你求婚？
So when's Money Bags popping the question?
我很肯定应该是在明天
I'm pretty sure tomorrow.
他要带我去
He's taking me out
一家在Hamptons的非常好的旅馆
to a really nice restaurant out in the Hamptons.
旅馆就建在水上
It's right on the water,
所以在我们漫步在沙滩 沐浴在月光之中
so afterwards we'll take a walk on the beach in the moonlight.
你也许该离开了
You should probably go.
我不懂诶 听起来是个不错的暗示
I don't know. It sounds pretty intimate.
(尴尬的笑)
我是认真的，我觉得我让你误会了
I'm serious. I feel like I misled you.
女士，我过来是帮你洗盘子的
Madam, I came here to wash your dishes.
没别的了
Nothing more.
- Whoa!刚才那是什么？！ - 什么是什么？
- Whoa! What was that!? - What was what?
这人和Barney 刚才对了个眼！
This guy and Barney just shared a look!
你认识他么?
Do you know him?
又来了！
They did it again!
整个事情就是个阴谋 绝对的！
This whole thing stinks, I tells ya!
阴谋！
It stinks!
Lily,你是在说Barney 花了六个月
Lily, are you really suggesting that Barney spent six months
为了学习一个他更本就不喜欢的烹饪招式而
commuting back and forth to Hoboken
在纽约和Hoboken之间折返
to learn a signature cooking style of a restaurant
仅仅是为了赢一场打赌
he doesn't even like so he could win a bet
甚至这打赌当时还根本不存在
he hadn't even made yet?
对的，整个事情就是个阴谋！
Yeah, the whole thing stinks.
不，这根本不可能
No, it's not possible, okay?
是我提议去Shinjitsu...
I was the one who said let's go to Shinjitsu...
(Barney打喷嚏) 注意身体
Bless you.
Barney怎么可能...
How could Barney have...
你这个天才的混蛋
You brilliant bastard.
这太明显了...
It's all so obvious now.
迄今为止， 我忘了，大概五年
For the past, oh, I don't know how long, five years,
每一次我说出，我们去"Shinjitsu"吧
every time I've said, "Let's go to Shinjitsu""
注意身体
Bless you.
你就会打喷嚏
You've sneezed.
每一次
Every time.
MARSHALL: 一点又一点
And little by little...
咱们去Shinjitsu.
Let's go to Shinjitsu.
注意身体
Bless you. Bless you.
...在我脑海之中 .你嵌入了这个遐想
...you forged the association in my brain.
那么我们去哪里吃饭
So what should we do for dinner?
我们去Shinjitsu. (喷嚏)
Let's go to Shinjitsu.
噢，注意身体， 谢谢
Oh, bless you. Thanks.
MARSHALL: 直到最终...
Until eventually...
是的，我是说过 我们周日才回来
Yes, I know I said that we'd be back Sunday,
但是那又怎么样 我们现在已经回来了
but guess what? We are back now!
现在到底...
Now what on earth...
别跳了 你到底...
Stop bouncing! What on earth
怎么想的 觉得我们会同意这个！
would make you think that we'd be okay with this?
咱们去Shinjitsu吧.
Let's go to Shinjitsu.
去年你每感冒一次
When you were sick for a week last year,
我们就去Shinjitsu 去了六次
I had Shinjitsu like six times.
你的确有这刀法...
You had the knife skills...
你握有把柄...
you had the trigger...
你所等待的 就是想要从我这里获得什么
All you needed then was to want something from me.
直到有一天 你想要的东西出现了
And then one day... those somethings came a-busting out.
Wapowng!
我要带着这样的念头生活
I am gonna have to walk this earth,
Barney要摸我的胸部
knowing Barney has touched my boobs.
是的，这个念头会伴随你
Yeah. It stays with you.
更别提他会用email来提醒你
His email reminders don't help.
Okay, Lily, 这太荒谬了
Okay, Lily, this is ridiculous.
如果你要取消 这个打赌的话
If you want to call the bet off...
太好了，打赌取消
Great! The bet's off!
让我说完
Let me finish.
条件是这样的:假如你同意让我看他们--
If you let me just see them--
不摸，仅仅是看-- 一分钟...
no touching, just looking-- for one minute...
30秒 好吧，30秒
30 seconds. For 30 seconds,
在一个亮堂堂的摄影室里
in a well-lit photography studio...
- 在小胡同里 - 在小胡同里...
- In the alley. - In the alley...
我们就彻底取消 这场赌约
then we'll cancel this entire wager completely.
成交么？
Do we have a deal?
我觉得你应该跟他成交
I totally think you should take the deal.
MARSHALL: 我不知道，我觉得我们还有机会
I don't think we have a choice.
我同意这场交易
Go on, take the deal.
好吧，我会认真考虑一下的
I'll... think about it.
那么你洗完盘子
So you're doing the dishes...
我洗完了盘子
I'm doing the dishes.
都搞定了
All done.
谢谢你！
Congratulations.
你的业报终于了结了 带着淡淡的柠檬香
Your karmic slate is clean and lemony fresh.
- 干杯. - 干杯.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
我终于可以重新开始
See, now I can start anew,
满心期待的憧憬 你和他...
and hopefully end up as happy as you and, uh...
请问他的名字是？
Sorry, what's his name?
- 谁的名字? - 即将称为你未婚夫...
- Whose name? - Your fiancé-to-be.
Oh! 他的名字是Klaus.
Oh! His name is Klaus.
- Klaus. - Klaus.
德国人.
German name.
- 是的，德国人 - Hmm.
- Yeah, German guy. - Hmm.
你在德国生活的时候
When you were living in Germany,
我们在坚持着异地恋...
and we were doing the whole long-distance thing...
那个Klaus 是不是在你班里?
wasn't there a Klaus in your class?
是有一个Klaus在我班里
There was a Klaus in my class.
- 而你和Klaus非常亲密 - 没有那么亲密
- And you and Klaus were close. - Not that close.
是是，你和你班里的Klaus十分亲密
Yes, yes, you and the Klaus from your class were quite close.
有点亲密
Kind of close.
- 是那个Klaus么? - 我的Klaus?
- Was that your Klaus? - My Klaus?
- 在你班里. - 在我班里?
- In your class. - In my class?
你的那个Klaus 是那个你们班跟你有点亲密的Klaus么?
Is your Klaus the kind of close Klaus from your class?
是的
Yes.
你每跟Klaus出轨吧？
You didn't cheat on me with Klaus, did you?
- 不不，我没有 - Mm.
- No. No, I did not. - Mm.
新的问题
Okay, new question.
在我们分手之后
After we broke up, how long were you single
你跟Klaus花了多久时间在一起?
before you and Klaus started dating?
噢，多久,um,我们是在四月分手的 ...
Oh, how long... um, well, we broke up in April, so...
一天半
a day and a half.
我了个去，您老不是在开玩笑吧!
Oh, you have got to be kidding me!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我花了六年的时间 来谴责自己
So I've spent the last six years feeling like
因为我背叛了你 结果你...
I completely betrayed you, when in truth, you...
好吧，是你逼我的
No, you know what?
(吐槽：好恶心)
我去
Okay. Fine.
就让你自己免于良心的谴责吧
Just let yourself off the hook on a technicality!
别忘了，是你先背叛我的
Forget the fact that you did cheat on me!
我怎么能忘 我永远不会忘
Forget it? I will never forget it. Okay?
我的歉意一直没有停过
I will never stop regretting it,
因为你对我意味着 太多太多！
because what we had meant that much to me!
我仅仅... 我希望我对你也意味着一些东西
I just... I wish it had meant something to you, too.
你开玩笑么？
Are you kidding?
- 我爱过你！ - 你爱过么?
- I loved you! - Did you?
是的
Yes.
我们在一起 曾经有过美妙的时光
We had such an amazing time together.
你还记得那个夜晚么
Do you remember that night
我们找到了Barney的疯狂视频?
we found that crazy videotape of Barney?
那个游戏之夜
Game night.
我们玩了一晚上 Marshall发明的优秀
We played that ridiculous game Marshall invented.
- Marshgammon. - 是的
- Marshgammon. - Yeah.
在那之后我们又玩了几次 但是我一直都学不会
We've played it a few times since. I still don't get it.
记得我们相识的晚上么
Remember the night we met?
我记得你 不让我亲你
I remember you not letting me kiss you.
记得为什么么？
Remember why?
你有一个可笑的想法
You had this ridiculous idea
你觉得亲你之前的那一个时刻...
that the moment leading up to the kiss...
那个等待..
The drum roll.
...就跟亲吻本身一样的美妙
...is as good as the kiss itself.
难道不是么
Isn't it?
这时刻更加的纯真
Well, it's certainly more innocent.
彻底的无瑕
It's completely harmless.
彻底的
Completely.
- Oh, 天哪! - Oh 不.
- Oh, my God! - Oh no.
不，不不不不
No, no-no-no-no-no.
- 我不该这么做的 - 不，是我的错
- I should not have done that. - No, that was me.
我让你过来帮我洗盘子！
I let you come wash my dishes!
我说我的 "烤箱" 需要 "清理"!
I said my "oven" needed "cleaning"!
我给了你不良暗示!
I invited you into a porno!
不
No.
我们都没错，这就是命运
You were right. This is fate.
我要再一次的 遇见你
I needed to see you one more time
去测试我对Klaus的感情.
in order to know for sure about Klaus.
结论是...?
And...?
结论是...
And...
我要去赶巴士
I have a bus to catch.
好吧，你可以看我的胸部
Fine, you can see my boobs!
去巷子里！
To the alley!
这不公平！
This seems unfair.
你看 我是惟一一个
I mean, I get that I'm the only person
不能看这个的 但...
not allowed to see this, but...
这个一点都不公平.
it just, it-it seems unfair.
快点, Lily, 快脱吧
Come on, Lily, hurry up.
哥们儿们...
Guys...
我是这场赌局的见证人，但是谁邀请了Takumi?
You know, I'm all for honoring a bet, but who invited Takumi?
对不起兄弟， 哥尽力了
Sorry, bro. I tried.
(我给你传照片)
发生了什么？ 我错过了什么？
What's going on? What am I missing?
小兔兔出来了么？ 长什么样子？
Are they out yet? What do they look like?
我不想知道具体描述
Look, I don't want to know!
可以用硬币大小给我比划
Just tell me the kind of coin.
你知不知道30秒究竟 有多长?
Do you know how long 30 seconds is?
你大概要花5秒钟...
It's going to be five seconds of...
然后是25秒钟...
followed by 25 seconds of....
我知道看Lily的兔兔
I mean, yes, seeing Lily's boobs
是你一直都想干的 但是得了吧
is all you've ever wanted, but come on.
他一直都想干的...
All he's ever wanted...
Lily,停!
Lily, stop!
你看不出来么?
Don't you see?
他计划这个很久了！
This was his plan all along!
他让我们相信他会玩Shinjitsu的各种技术,
He let us think he knows how to do all this Shinjitsu stuff,
让他把你带到这里来
just so he could get you out here
引兔出洞！
whipping out your milk-makers!
你个混蛋!
You son of a bitch!
赌局又回来了!
The bet is back on!
干得不错,Barney!
Nice try, Barney!
干的不错
Nice try.
（放荡的大小）
(Barney帅呆了，有木有！！！)
也许我错了
Maybe I was wrong.
我觉得我已经完成了你们要让我做的事了?
Well, I guess that's everything you asked me to do, is it not?
噢，等等! 让虾飞入口袋.
Oh, wait! The shrimp in the pocket.
经典中的经典
A modern classic.
现在...
And now...
在二垒上整整一分钟...
for one minute on second base...
坚挺又下流的挤压...
with a firm yet sensual squeeze...
没什么能阻止他了
Nothing can stop him now.
只有一件可以！
One thing can.
实际上是两件
Make that two things.
不！
No!!
Yeah! Yeah!
那么你们去巴士那边...
So you take her to the bus...
我带她去坐巴士
I take her to the bus.
场景何其相似
Well, this feels familiar.
你要离开 希望我说"不要走"
You leaving, me kind of wanting to say, "Don't go""
现在有点迟了
Little late for that.
是有点
Little bit.
- 不要走 - Ted...
- Don't go. - Ted...
对不起，有点失态...
I'm sorry. I just...
我为什么那时候不说出来
Why didn't I say it then?
为什么我要让你上飞机？
Why'd I let you get on that plane?
为什么我不跟你一起走？
Why didn't I get on it with you?
要是我们现在生活在一起，要是我们能...
What would our lives be right now, if we had just...
Hold住?
held on?
我还会在今晚的宴会上遇到你么...
Would I have still run into you at this party tonight...
或者 我们今夜会出现在这里么?
or would we have been there together?
我们携手归家...
We'd go home...
归我们的家?
to our home?
你做饭来我洗碗
You cook. I do the dishes.
我快乐因为你快乐
I'm happy that you're happy.
但，现实太悲摧了
But damn it.
要是？
What if?
你是不是想听这个问题的答案？
Do you really want to know the answer to that?
不
No.
我觉得这个答案会让我难过
I think it would kill me.
再见，Ted.
Good-bye, Ted.
故事结束了
And that was it.
现在她大概订婚了
Now she's probably engaged.
也许这是最好的结局了
Maybe it's for the best.
好了，现在...
All right. Well...
我们要出去了鸭
We're gonna duck out.
不好意思要让你买单了
Sorry to leave you with the bill.
噢，弟兄们 这会是美好的一年啊！
Oh, guys, it's gonna be a good year.
我很高兴你们开心
I'm glad you guys can laugh,
因为我觉得我又要生病了
'cause I think I'm gonna be physically ill.
变得跟只绿头鸭一样?
Coming down with a mallardy?
噢，他们看起来饿了
Oh, they look hungry. There you go.
来开饭了～
Here you go.
NARRATOR: 孩子们实际上 我忽略了故事的一部分
Kids, there was one part I left out.
再见， Ted.
Good-bye, Ted.
好吧，答案究竟是什么?
Okay, yes. What's the answer?
因为一个原因， 所以我们永远不会在一起
There is a reason that it didn't work out between you and me,
不是因为异地恋
but it's not Germany.
我打赌这个原因
And I'm willing to bet it's the same reason none of your other
也是你这六年一直单身的原因
relationships in the last six years have lasted either.
是Robin.
It's Robin.
不
No.
是的
Yes.
她对你的影响 远远大于你所认知的
She is so much bigger in your world than you realize.
而你现在的所做 你，Robin和Barney
And this thing that you're all doing, you and Barney and Robin,
你们三人一起在酒吧玩 泡夜店
where the three of you hang out at the bar night in, night out,
你们之间仅仅是哥们儿关系么?
like you're all just buddies?
没那么简单，相信我
That doesn't work. Trust me.
你肯定错了
You-You've got it all wrong.
我肯定对了
I'm right about this.
再见, Ted.
Good-bye, Ted.
NARRATOR: 事实表明, 她的确是对的.
And sure enough, she was right.
的确没那么简单; 只是我当时不愿意承认罢了
It didn't work; we just didn't realize it yet.
== sync, corrected by elderman == == 翻译，调整，字幕by Saraphines == ==  @FDUPT首发 == 真是不易啊！！！
== sync, corrected by elderman ==